{
    "id": "8469e40eb7e246cb837a2bf143ebb4a1",
    "title": "Simple Present vs. Simple Past",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Dad …………………. tea in the morning, but today he ......................... coffee.",
            "description": "The simple present is used to talk about habitual actions.",
            "answers": [
                "drinks, drank",
                "drinks, drinks",
                "drank, drinks"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2a8df6caa2de4a05b40e4138ff68ce41"
        },
        {
            "question": "All children ……………………….. love.",
            "description": "We use the simple present to talk about general truths.",
            "answers": [
                "need",
                "needed",
                "needs"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f065ad8bc7614ffebaefaa08ff658401"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………… a strange dream yesterday.",
            "description": "The simple past is used to talk about finished events.",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d4215db1a19f4a8cb30b530e00eae007"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………… a Sci-fi movie yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "watch",
                "watched"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3d3fe299feff4512be282524b1d20df4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………… my phone while I was on vacation in Greece.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lose",
                "losed",
                "lost"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4e39e614573f44c2a01a22eb1460fb9f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………………. gently to the child.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "speaks",
                "spoke"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "98a40243dfcf487d86d66d119203f70f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plants ………………………. carbon dioxide and release oxygen.",
            "description": "Use the simple present to talk about a general truth.",
            "answers": [
                "absorb",
                "absorbed"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b0d8334b6ca744a9842eb4242d143072"
        },
        {
            "question": "Kind words ………………………. others happy.",
            "description": "Use the simple present to talk about a general truth.",
            "answers": [
                "make",
                "made"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "714d77a90d24427d8429e944b19d9d24"
        },
        {
            "question": "Birds ……………………… in the sky.",
            "description": "Use the simple present to talk about a general truth.",
            "answers": [
                "fly",
                "flies",
                "flew"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "67151fb3be4b49028168ee4f2f1e8b7f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Money ……………………… on trees.",
            "description": "Use the simple present to talk about a general truth.",
            "answers": [
                "do not grow",
                "does not grow",
                "did not grow"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "24a7c86ddfea40aa94ee1bee0a69e587"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ……………………… the car to pay off the loan.",
            "description": "The simple past is used to talk about finished events.",
            "answers": [
                "sold",
                "sell",
                "had sold"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "de582b93972644a6affb0f6ef35ce84d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………. me a story the other day.",
            "description": "The simple past is used to talk about finished events.",
            "answers": [
                "tell",
                "told",
                "has told"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "324d5a8a1d984ec2b989e5cfaf72decc"
        }
    ]
}